all right let's talk about music okay so
in the morning we do music and in order
to play your favorite music uh you can
do exclamation point YT stands for
YouTube and then space and then paste
the URL or the ID of the song you want
to hear you can't do names and stuff
like that you got to do the actual
video and then it will be entered into
the queue for me to decide whether we're
play it or not um if you want to take
back your video you can do exclamation
point wrong video all one word if you
want
to skip the current video because you
don't like it you can put your vote in
exclamation point Skip and I think it's
five and then that will skip the video
and if you want to know what the current
video is exclamation point video will
tell you the name it'll give you the URL
to the video so you can go look it up
and if you like the song that's playing
right now now that those are the
commands but this is the policy I play
what I want so no matter when it is if I
don't like your video I'm going to skip
it and don't be offended it just means
that I don't want to spend time on a
video that I don't want to hear um this
isn't about me entertaining you with
your videos that you want me to see this
is about you finding things that I want
to watch or I want to listen to and then
I'll pick the ones that I want to listen
listen to and if you don't have the same
taste as me that's totally cool um but
I'm okay with anything if you submit
anything that's got uh bad stuff in it
including the nword will ban you so
don't submit stuff that is going to be
not PG-13 that wouldn't be playable on
the public radio station period that's
your only warning thanks talk to you
later